[{"answer": "Wow, this has been a good game so far.  I really thought it would be a blow", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 16, "question": "", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " The Mets are New Yorks team, right, Dennis?  Oh, what about the New Yor", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 20, "question": "Wow, this has been a good game so far.  I really thought it would be a blow", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " New York is such a big city that it has two teams, the Mets and the Yankees", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 24, "question": " The Mets are New Yorks team, right, Dennis?  Oh, what about the New Yor", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " Ok, so explain to me again what is happening on the screen right now", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 28, "question": " New York is such a big city that it has two teams, the Mets and the Yankees", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " Well, see, the Braves are up at bat.  That means they are on offense.  Th", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 29, "question": " Ok, so explain to me again what is happening on the screen right now", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " Oh!  He just hit the ball.  Now hes running", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 33, "question": " Well, see, the Braves are up at bat.  That means they are on offense.  Th", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " Right.  After the batter hits the ball, he tries to run to that base.  If he can ge", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Oh!  He just hit the ball.  Now hes running", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " Hmm.  I can almost guess how the rules go if I watch it for a while, but ho", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 44, "question": " Right.  After the batter hits the ball, he tries to run to that base.  If he can ge", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": "Each team gets three outs, then they switch sides.  You know how the ball go", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 48, "question": " Hmm.  I can almost guess how the rules go if I watch it for a while, but ho", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " Yeah", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 52, "question": "Each team gets three outs, then they switch sides.  You know how the ball go", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " Well, he didnt get to stay on the base because he is out.  You can also get a", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Yeah", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " It seems like fun", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 58, "question": " Well, he didnt get to stay on the base because he is out.  You can also get a", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " It is fun.  I played on a team when I was younger.  I think I played for abou", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 59, "question": " It seems like fun", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " Wow!  Were you any good", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 63, "question": " It is fun.  I played on a team when I was younger.  I think I played for abou", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " I think I was pretty good.  I mean, I was better than a lot of my teammates", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 64, "question": " Wow!  Were you any good", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": "What position did you play on your team", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 65, "question": " I think I was pretty good.  I mean, I was better than a lot of my teammates", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " I played several different positions on the field.  A lot of the time I was ", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 66, "question": "What position did you play on your team", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " The boss?  What do you mean", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 71, "question": " I played several different positions on the field.  A lot of the time I was ", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " Well, pitchers are very important.  They control the game on defense", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 72, "question": " The boss?  What do you mean", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " Oh, I see.  Hey, could you teach me how to play", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 76, "question": " Well, pitchers are very important.  They control the game on defense", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " Sure.  I could take you to some batting cages and let you practice hittin", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 77, "question": " Oh, I see.  Hey, could you teach me how to play", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " Hey, that really does sound like fun.  Maybe we could go to a baseball gam", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 79, "question": " Sure.  I could take you to some batting cages and let you practice hittin", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " Of course we can.  Its a whole different experience to actually see the game i", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 87, "question": " Hey, that really does sound like fun.  Maybe we could go to a baseball gam", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " Oooh, now Im getting excited.  How much are tickets to a game", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 91, "question": " Of course we can.  Its a whole different experience to actually see the game i", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": " Actually, theyre not that much.  Prices range from $1 for standing room onl", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 92, "question": " Oooh, now Im getting excited.  How much are tickets to a game", "qSentId": 91},{"answer": " Thats not too bad.  Wow, I can hardly wait to go to my first baseball game.  ", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 96, "question": " Actually, theyre not that much.  Prices range from $1 for standing room onl", "qSentId": 95},{"answer": " Oh, another thing thats special about going to see a baseball game is th", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 100, "question": " Thats not too bad.  Wow, I can hardly wait to go to my first baseball game.  ", "qSentId": 99},{"answer": " What do you mean a great souvenir", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 104, "question": " Oh, another thing thats special about going to see a baseball game is th", "qSentId": 103},{"answer": " Sometimes the batter will hit the ball into the stands where the fans are sitting", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 105, "question": " What do you mean a great souvenir", "qSentId": 104},{"answer": " Really?  You dont have to give it back", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 109, "question": " Sometimes the batter will hit the ball into the stands where the fans are sitting", "qSentId": 108},{"answer": " Nope.  If you can get the ball, its yours to keep, but its kinda rare to actuall", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 110, "question": " Really?  You dont have to give it back", "qSentId": 109},{"answer": " Well, Im feeling lucky.  Lets buy some good tickets and try to catch a ball", "docId": "08-06", "aSentId": 114, "question": " Nope.  If you can get the ball, its yours to keep, but its kinda rare to actuall", "qSentId": 113}]
